JAMES TENCE

647-216-9396 | james.tence@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Junior UX/UI Designer with 1 year of successful experience in fast-paced and project-oriented settings. A team-player with expertise completing various design-based tasks, Visual design, Web Re-Designs and Mobile App UX/UI design and conceptualization. Looking to obtain a UX Designer Role in an ethical and diverse company with the opportunity to learn new skills.

SKILLS

- Microsoft Office
- Executive and Medical related Recruiting
- Figma
- Adobe Suites
- Miro
- Data Organization
- Salesforce

- Staff Management and Scheduling
- Visual design
- UX/UI design for Websites and Mobile
- User Experience
 Research and Qualitative interviewing experience.
- Human Resources experience
- Multitasking Abilities
- Analytical Skills
- Conflict Resolution

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Junior UX/UI Designer | University of Toronto – Bootcamp Program | September 2023 – Present

University of Toronto UX/UI Bootcamp Program, ON-Remote

- User Research: Conducting initial and final User interviews in a professional manner to obtain information for the re-iteration of a website or a mobile application.
- Wireframing and Prototyping: Created and conceptualized sketches, low fidelity wireframe structures and further developed them into High Fidelity wireframes for display and presentation.
- Visual Design: Designed, created and collaborated to prepare ready to use UX/UI style guides for general wireframes and prototypes.
- Worked as a junior designer on a Government website re-design project on Canada Post as well as in a team setting and collaborated with a design team to re-design a Non-Government

Organization website (Food Banks of Canada) and a Mobile Application (conceptualized design that works as an extension for Spotify.

Scheduler/Recruiter | Parkview Home Long Term Care. | August 2019 - Present Stouffville, ON- Hybrid/Remote

- Completion of daily projects as assigned by management in a timely manner.
- Processing in the reconciliation of resident monthly bills
- Daily staffing and scheduling within the Nursing department (PSWs and Registered Staff).
- Created staff manuals and communicated deadlines to completed projects on time.
- Communicating daily updates to staff and clients regarding Public Health protocol through online education seminars and Email.
- Created and implemented forward-thinking initiatives to improve employee engagement.

EDUCATION

User Experience and User Interface Bootcamp Certification Program | University of Toronto | Certification | September 2023 – Present

Bachelor of Fine Arts (BFA) in Drawing and Painting | Ontario College of Art and Design University | Degree | September 2011 - October 2014

References available upon request.